goplan.org 2011-03-18

# Goplan: Privacy Policy

## Our privacy policy

This policy in short: any data you upload is yours, and we'll never use or share it with anyone. 

Goplan (Product) and its website (Site) are property of Webreakstuff, Lda. All our contact details are available here.

### About the Privacy Policy

We at Webreakstuff ("we" or Webreakstuff) have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. This privacy policy only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage, and data gathered, on the goplan.org, goplanapp.com and goplan.info websites (and sub-domains) but does not apply to any other Website or offline point of contact between webreakstuff.com, or any other company, and consumers. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. This privacy policy was last revised on January 25, 2007. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time.

### Information Gathering

Like most commerce Websites, each time you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the Site for you and to diagnose problems with our Site, we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

We collect only the domain name of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as site registrations. The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for any purposes. We use cookies to record session information, such as Goplan login information or interface customization.

### Disclosure

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., subscription dates or payments) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address. We may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

### Security

We do not keep or handle with any type of sensitive financial information, as all our transactions are at this time processed by PayPal.

### Data Storage

Webreakstuff uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Goplan. Although Webreakstuff owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Goplan application, you retain all rights to your data.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

### Changes

We will never use or share customer information for any purpose other than Goplan's normal usage. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
